{
    "subject": "resource/Noshi_Gilani",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/Pakistan",
    "human_readable": "Noshi Gilani's nationality is Pakistan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9448716044425964,
            "question": "Is Noshi Gilani Pakistani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8984191417694092,
            "question": "What is Noshi Gilani's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8757529258728027,
            "question": "Identify the nationality of Noshi Gilani."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6200318932533264,
            "question": "Noshi Gilani's citizenship is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6141747832298279,
            "question": "From which country does Noshi Gilani originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663771629333496,
            "question": "Where was Noshi Gilani born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5414116382598877,
            "question": "To what nation does Noshi Gilani belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48828771710395813,
            "question": "What is Noshi Gilani's national identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48826104402542114,
            "question": "What country considers Noshi Gilani as its citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4779984951019287,
            "question": "Where is Noshi Gilani from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noshi Gilani's nationality is Pakistan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7399_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country considers Noshi Gilani as its citizen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7399_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Noshi Gilani's national identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7399_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what nation does Noshi Gilani belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7399_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7399_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\nNoshi Gilani's nationality is Pakistan.\n\nAfter reviewing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nIndeed, all the documents mention that Noshi Gilani was born in Bahawalpur, Pakistan, and there is no indication of her having a different nationality."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Noshi Gilani was born in Bahawalpur, Pakistan and is described as a Pakistani Urdu poet. This supports the statement that her nationality is Pakistan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}